mondera.com 2002-01-26

# Mondera.com - Help (Privacy Policy)

**The Information We Need to Process Your Order**

You explicitly provide information via: 

  * New Account Form or Contact with Customer Service 

\- To process your order, we require your name, phone number, billing address, email address, shipping address and credit card information.  
\- We only use this information to create your account and/or to process your order. If any questions arise about your order we will contact you first by email and then, if necessary, by phone.  
\- We share only necessary information with the third parties that are involved in the order process, such as the financial institution that issued your credit card, the shipping carrier and Mondera customer service representatives. (NOTE: We would be obligated to disclose individual personal information if Mondera were to be subpoenaed or ordered by a court of law.) 

We Automatically Collect 

  * Shopper ID 

\- Upon visiting our site, we assigned you a unique Shopper ID in the form of a cookie. We use this ID to keep track of your shopping basket during your visit and to identify you as a repeat visitor.  
\- If you would rather not be identified as a repeat visitor, we recommend that you disable the cookie support in your browser. 

  * Internet Protocol (IP) Address

\- We record your IP address each time you visit Mondera. Recording IP addresses helps us determine usage and traffic patterns. 

Other Information We Collect

  * Feedback Form

\- Should you contact us through our feedback form, we require your name and email address only to send you a reply.  
\- If you use the form to send comments about your shopping experience at Mondera, we may include the comment with your name in our [Customer Testimonials](http://www.mondera.com/about/testimonials.asp?mscssid=RKMHA6R4WBS92KNW00AKHCAVB3QGB7UB) section. 

  * Email Newsletter," "Email Special Offers" and "Catalog" Sign-up Features

\- Should you participate in these services we will only use the information you provide to promote Mondera services and products.   
\- We will not share any personal information with third parties. 
* **Service Providers** Mondera works with an outside vendor called Angara E-Commerce Services to dynamically personalize our web site. While providing this personalization service, Angara may place cookies on your machine and may collect certain anonymous information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visit. We do not provide any of your personally identifiable information to Angara. To learn about Angara's privacy policy and how to opt-out of the service, see [www.angara.com/privacy/index.cfm](http://www.angara.com/privacy/index.cfm). 

**Sharing**

  * Personal Information is Not Shared

Aside from the previously mentioned third parties involved in the processing of your order, we do not share your personally identifiable information with any other entities without your express permission. 
  * External Links

Our site may include links to other sites. If you decide to follow these links, we are not responsible for the privacy policies and content of these sites. Generally, we will inform you of these links. 

**Your Consent**  
By using our website, you consent to the usage and collection of this information. If we decide to alter our privacy policy, these changes will be posted on this page so that you will always be informed about what information is collected, how it is used, and under what circumstances it will be disclosed. 

**Contacting Us**

  * Account Changes and Deletions 
    * Changes

\- If you created an account and would like to change your account, please call Customer Service toll-free at 1 (800) MONDERA or send an email with your changes to [customerservice@mondera.com](mailto:customerservice@mondera.com) and include the email address with which you registered. We will send a confirmation request to that email address and after receiving your reply, will update your account within 48 hours. 

    * Deletions

If you created an account and would like to delete your account, please send an email to [customerservice@mondera.com](mailto:customerservice@mondera.com) and include the email address with which you registered. We will send a confirmation request to that email address and upon receiving your reply, delete your account. 

  * If you have any questions or comments regarding this statement, please contact [customerservice@mondera.com](mailto:customerservice@mondera.com). If your inquiry has not been responded to or satisfactorily addressed, please contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/users/users_watchdog.html). 

Mondera's Web pages may contain Web beacons placed there by Avenue A, to help determine the effectiveness of Internet advertising campaigns. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, "[click here](http://www.avenuea.com/info/optout.asp)." 
**The Information We Need to Process Your Order**

You explicitly provide information via: 

  * New Account Form or Contact with Customer Service 

\- To process your order, we require your name, phone number, billing address, email address, shipping address and credit card information.  
\- We only use this information to create your account and/or to process your order. If any questions arise about your order we will contact you first by email and then, if necessary, by phone.  
\- We share only necessary information with the third parties that are involved in the order process, such as the financial institution that issued your credit card, the shipping carrier and Mondera customer service representatives. (NOTE: We would be obligated to disclose individual personal information if Mondera were to be subpoenaed or ordered by a court of law.) 

We Automatically Collect 

  * Shopper ID 

\- Upon visiting our site, we assigned you a unique Shopper ID in the form of a cookie. We use this ID to keep track of your shopping basket during your visit and to identify you as a repeat visitor.  
\- If you would rather not be identified as a repeat visitor, we recommend that you disable the cookie support in your browser. 

  * Internet Protocol (IP) Address

\- We record your IP address each time you visit Mondera. Recording IP addresses helps us determine usage and traffic patterns. 

Other Information We Collect

  * Feedback Form

\- Should you contact us through our feedback form, we require your name and email address only to send you a reply.  
\- If you use the form to send comments about your shopping experience at Mondera, we may include the comment with your name in our [Customer Testimonials](http://www.mondera.com/about/testimonials.asp?mscssid=9V86L6VA0D4X8KSW72ADGSHULVKXFN90) section. 

  * Email Newsletter," "Email Special Offers" and "Catalog" Sign-up Features

\- Should you participate in these services we will only use the information you provide to promote Mondera services and products.   
\- We will not share any personal information with third parties. 
* **Service Providers** Mondera works with an outside vendor called Angara E-Commerce Services to dynamically personalize our web site. While providing this personalization service, Angara may place cookies on your machine and may collect certain anonymous information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visit. We do not provide any of your personally identifiable information to Angara. To learn about Angara's privacy policy and how to opt-out of the service, see [www.angara.com/privacy/index.cfm](http://www.angara.com/privacy/index.cfm). 

**Sharing**

  * Personal Information is Not Shared

Aside from the previously mentioned third parties involved in the processing of your order, we do not share your personally identifiable information with any other entities without your express permission. 
  * External Links

Our site may include links to other sites. If you decide to follow these links, we are not responsible for the privacy policies and content of these sites. Generally, we will inform you of these links. 

**Your Consent**  
By using our website, you consent to the usage and collection of this information. If we decide to alter our privacy policy, these changes will be posted on this page so that you will always be informed about what information is collected, how it is used, and under what circumstances it will be disclosed. 

**Contacting Us**

  * Account Changes and Deletions 
    * Changes

\- If you created an account and would like to change your account, please call Customer Service toll-free at 1 (800) MONDERA or send an email with your changes to [customerservice@mondera.com](mailto:customerservice@mondera.com) and include the email address with which you registered. We will send a confirmation request to that email address and after receiving your reply, will update your account within 48 hours. 

    * Deletions

If you created an account and would like to delete your account, please send an email to [customerservice@mondera.com](mailto:customerservice@mondera.com) and include the email address with which you registered. We will send a confirmation request to that email address and upon receiving your reply, delete your account. 

  * If you have any questions or comments regarding this statement, please contact [customerservice@mondera.com](mailto:customerservice@mondera.com). If your inquiry has not been responded to or satisfactorily addressed, please contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/users/users_watchdog.html). 

Mondera's Web pages may contain Web beacons placed there by Avenue A, to help determine the effectiveness of Internet advertising campaigns. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, "[click here](http://www.avenuea.com/info/optout.asp)."
